charmboard.com 2019-06-23

# Privacy - Charmboard

**Privacy Policy**

Charmboard recognizes the importance of maintaining your privacy. We value your privacy and appreciate your trust in us. This Policy describes about information we collect from you, why we collect it, what we do with it and what choices do you have. We have tried to keep this policy simple and meaning full. In case you need any help or clarification please write to us at **feedback@charmboard.com**.

##### Information we collect

 **A.Information you allow us to collect**

When you use our services, you give us certain information voluntarily. Such information may include your name, profile photo, likes, charm, comments, address, phone number, posts, language you speak etc. If you use our services on a mobile device, you also provide us location data.

You may allow us to collect information from other services such as Facebook, Twitter or Google or from any other source. In such cases, you allow us to collect information from those accounts, which may include your contracts, friends, photos etc.

 **B.Technical information collected by us**

Whenever you use a website, mobile application or other Internet service, certain information is created and stored automatically. Below are some types of technical information which we collect.

 **I.Cookie data**

Cookies are small text file stored by the browser (For example, Internet Explorer, Chrome etc). They allow websites to store things like user preferences. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows the Service or a third-party to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the service more useful to you. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. We place both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer.

You can decide whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not. If you haven't changed your computer's settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies. Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly. We recommend that you leave them turned on.

 **II.Log Data**

Whenever you use our services, our servers record certain information automatically (“log data”). These are the information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or that your mobile app sends when you’re using it. These data may include your Internet Protocol address, the address of the web pages you visited that had Charmboard features, browser type and settings, the date and time of your request, the time spent on those pages, how you used Charmboard, cookie data and other statistics.

 **III.Device information**

In addition to log data, we may also collect information such as type of device you are using, what operating system you are using, device settings, unique device identifiers and crash data. Collection of such data often depends on what type of device you’re using and its settings. For example, different types of information are available depending on whether you’re using a Mac or a PC, or an iPhone or Android phone. To learn more about what information your device makes available to us, please also check the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider.

 **C.Information shared by our third party**

We may get information about you including your activity from our partners, affiliates, agencies or any third party.

##### Use of Information we collect

 **A.Improved User satisfaction**

We use personal data to provide the services you request or otherwise described to you at the time of collection. We also use your data to;

  * troubleshoot problems
  * help promote a safe service
  * measure consumer interest in our products and services
  * inform you about online and offline offers, product, services and updates
  * customize your experience
  * detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity
  * enforce our terms and conditions
  * improve our product and service offerings

We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website, to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

We may ask you to participate in optional surveys. Our objective is collect certain information such as contact information and demographic information, which helps us in improving your experience at our website and providing you with the content that which we think might be useful or interesting for you.

 **B.Sharing of personal information**

We may share your personal information to;

  * advertisers to collect information on Charmboard to audit the delivery and performance of their ads. Advisors may appoint a third party to collect such information.
  * corporate entities and affiliates to;

a.help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts

b.correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services

c.facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity.

Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.​

  * officials or third party if it is required by law or in good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process.
  * law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to:

a.enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy

b.respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property

c.personal safety of our users or the general public.​​

  * a business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a transaction occur that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information?
  * other services such as Facebook, Twitter etc as per your request to do so.

 **C.Other use of personal information**

We use your name, profile picture, User content, information or any Charms created in connection with commercial, sponsored, or related content, served or enhanced by us. This means, for example, that you permit a business or other entity to pay us to display your name and/or profile picture with your content or information, or serve you communication in connection with the charms that you have created without any compensation to you.

You understand that we may not always identify paid services and communications as such

 **D.Collection of personal information by third party linked websites**

Our website may provide links to other third party websites. Such third party websites may collect personally identifiable information about you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked sites.

 **E.Collection of personal information by Advertisers**

We may use third-party to serve ads or other features across the Internet and on our website. Generally such third party collects anonymous information such as your visit to our site, time spend, your view, likes, comments, interactions etc. They may also use information about your visits to this and other sites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, address, email address, or any personally identifying information about the user.​

You can write to us at **feedback@charmboard.com** to know more about this information and the options you have.

##### Choices/Opt-Out

You can check your account sttings to know what choices you have about your information. You may set your browser to block all cookies. For example;

You can opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account. You can make your personal information private. For any clarification please e-mail your request to **feedback@charmboard.com**.

##### Information shared by Minor

As per terms of usage, we don’t allow minor to use our services without parental guidance. Please contact us at **feedback@charmboard.com** , if you feel that minor has provided any personal information without parental guidance.

##### Changes to the policy

We may change this policy from time to time and if we do we’ll post any changes on this page. If you continue to use Charmboard after those changes are in effect, you agree to the revised policy. If the changes are significant, we may provide a more prominent notice or get your consent, as required by law.
